170705 Change Log:

Enhancements:
- Bees now transfer honey once they have gone in the beehive.
+ Hornet Spawning
	- Forest Beetle (forest 3) spawns 1 hornet
	- Forest 4 spawns tier one hornets with formula
	- Forest 5 spawns tier one/two hornets
	- Above Forest 6, fireflies and tier 1/2 hornets are spawnable
- Added fireflies with glowing effect. Kill fatigue make them red coloured
+ Guardian Training Panel
	- Training market demonstration 0%
	- Implementing Royal Guardian training gameplay 
	- After purchasing a training course, it will only be initiated the next round (would be a problem for guardians that take up half a week)
	- Once completed, the guardian will be returned as the upgraded guardian in 5s
	- Has its own training timer

Bug Fixes:
- Fixed bug when a bee / guardian is deselected on a flower, all bees would go towards that flower.


Known Bugs:
- "Stucking to border" fix
	- The fix works, but if the creature had a target, since the moveTheta is forcefully changed, it would not be able to reach its target correctly
- On some occasion the bee would miss out its target and cannot go to it properly (e.g. flower, beehive). Problem root unknown.

- In the Royal Guardian training course, guardian would often get stucked on borders and end up using the "stucked to border fix" which is not optimal