170711b Change Log:

Enhancements:
+ TRAINING GUARDIANS
  - Added Hunting Guardian (both course and mechanic)

+ TRAINING GUARDIAN SHOP
  - Made the guardians options unavailable after purchased, and when a course is ongoing. (This prevents possible bugs as well)

- Added the vector image of a ladybug (for hunting guardian)
- Added the class Ladybug (for hunting guardian)



Bug Fixes:
None



Known Bugs:
+ OLD BUGS
- "Stucking to border" fix
	- The fix works, but if the creature had a target, since the moveTheta is forcefully changed, it would not be able to reach its target correctly
- On some occasion the bee would miss out its target and cannot go to it properly (e.g. flower, beehive). Problem root unknown.

- In the Royal Guardian training course, guardian would often get stucked on borders and end up using the "stucked to border fix" which is not optimal

+ NEW BUGS
- When selected a guardian and pressed the beehive, it will not move towards it
- On rare occasions the bees (happee+) cannot enter beehive. (not first person experience)

+ CODE CLEANUP NOTES!!!
- Bee moving mechanic can be moved to Bee.pde
- Interation between bee and flower have lots of unnecessary variables
- Pick honey, go in flower, tell bee it's not inside flower   logic is ambigious - quite difficult to force the bee out of the fucking flower



