170707 Change Log:

Enhancements:
+ BEE APPEARANCE
	- Enlarged the size of bees by 1 pixel
	- Modified the overall appearance (added "zebra lines"!)

+ TECHNICAL
	- Changed the adding parameters of the Bee Class
	- Changed the adding paramters of the Hornet Class

+ SHOP
	- Added bee icons next to their corresponding buttons.
	- Added guardian icons next to their corresponding buttons.

+ GUARDIAN TRAINING
	- Added the training course for Baiting Guardian. (Course balance needed; Guardian functionality 0%. Only the course has been implemented.)

- Further nerf of honey price. Now honey price won't rise above 60 in the first half of the game.

Bug Fixes:
- Fixed the bug where the timer starts counting before the game has started.
- Fixed the visual bug where the bee's body is part transparent (mixes with other colours)
- Fixed the visual bug where the flower spawns with a constrained smallest size, not with 0

+ TECHNICAL
	- Realized that ellipse() uses diameter not radius... Replaced all bee "radius" to diameter. Might cause other bugs.




Known Bugs:
+ OLD BUGS
- "Stucking to border" fix
	- The fix works, but if the creature had a target, since the moveTheta is forcefully changed, it would not be able to reach its target correctly
- On some occasion the bee would miss out its target and cannot go to it properly (e.g. flower, beehive). Problem root unknown.

- In the Royal Guardian training course, guardian would often get stucked on borders and end up using the "stucked to border fix" which is not optimal

+ NEW BUGS
- When ending the round in guardian training tab with Baiting Guardian being the course having bought, a grey screen appears. (IM TOO TIRED TO FIND OUT THE ROOT TODAY)