170706b Change Log:

Enhancements:
+ Guardians
	- Nerfs to all guardian's sensing area. Player has to control the guardian better in order for them to auto-follow the enemies
	- Only upgraded guardians can kill fireflies now.

+ Fireflies
	- Fireflies are "scared" if upgraded guardians are in a certain radius. They would start flying in the guardian's direction in order to try to escape from them.

+ Market
	- Removed Royal Guardian's purchase & sell button
	- Removed Jumbee's purchase & sell button
	- All trained guardians are sellable in G. Training tab

+ Guardian Training
	- Training fireflies now shows a health bar instead of "2 taps" / "1 tap"

- Added a startup screen.
- Increased startup bee amount from 1 to 3.
- Player can now choose to "Sell All Honey" when the round is ending.
- Player now have access to market and graph (where the player can sell different amount of honey) in the forest choosing screen.
- Twerks to all creatures' flight speed. Balance still needed.
- The previous honey selling price now affects the next iteration's time (based on the OG game)


Bug Fixes:
- Fixed bug whe


Known Bugs:
- "Stucking to border" fix
	- The fix works, but if the creature had a target, since the moveTheta is forcefully changed, it would not be able to reach its target correctly
- On some occasion the bee would miss out its target and cannot go to it properly (e.g. flower, beehive). Problem root unknown.

- In the Royal Guardian training course, guardian would often get stucked on borders and end up using the "stucked to border fix" which is not optimal