170709 Change Log:

Enhancements:
- Now enemies cannot kill the bees that has not come out of beehive (although they can still camp the beehive)

- Baiting guardian mechanic done

Bug Fixes:
- Fixed the bug when ending the round in guardian training tab with Baiting Guardian being the course having bought, a grey screen appears. 
- Fixed the bug where sometimes hornets get removed instantly after spawning

+ TECHNICAL
	- Fixed the function calcMoveTheta(). Can be safely used now.



Known Bugs:
+ OLD BUGS
- "Stucking to border" fix
	- The fix works, but if the creature had a target, since the moveTheta is forcefully changed, it would not be able to reach its target correctly
- On some occasion the bee would miss out its target and cannot go to it properly (e.g. flower, beehive). Problem root unknown.

- In the Royal Guardian training course, guardian would often get stucked on borders and end up using the "stucked to border fix" which is not optimal

+ CODE CLEANUP NOTES!!!
- Bee moving mechanic can be moved to Bee.pde
- Mechanic that determine which flower the bee will go to lacks a "break;" - the cause of sometimes bees shifting to other flowers even though it's assigned with that particular flower
- Interation between bee and flower have lots of unnecessary variables
- Pick honey, go in flower, tell bee it's not inside flower   logic is ambigious - quite difficult to force the bee out of the fucking flower



hunting guardian course: create a trail by mouse dragging (cooldown ability with x duration); the guardian will go to that trail's starting pt.; if the trail circled the enemy then that enemy gets killed. different enemies give different points. if circled a bee deduct points.