170701 Change Log:

Enhancements:
- Fatigue for hornets which had just killed a bee (5s)
- Flower spawn animation



Bug Fixes:
None

Known Bugs:
- "Stucking to border" fix
	- The fix works, but if the creature had a target, since the moveTheta is forcefully changed, it would not be able to reach its target correctly
- HORNETS
	- The hornet spawn timer is not reset after each round, so it would accumulate after the first time the player has entered any hornet forests
- On some occasion the bee would miss out its target and cannot go to it properly. (e.g. flower, beehive)
- When a bee is picking honey, and the player tries to deselect that bee, it would cause all bees to fly to that flower