170718b Change Log:

Enhancements:
- Added tutorial
+ TECHNICAL
    - Moved the bee moving & pick honey mechanic to Bees.pde.
    - Made a function for mouse event (selectionMechanic())



Bug Fixes:
None



Known Bugs:
+ OLD BUGS
- "Stucking to border" fix
	- The fix works, but if the creature had a target, since the moveTheta is forcefully changed, it would not be able to reach its target correctly

- On some occasion the bee would miss out its target and cannot go to it properly (e.g. flower, beehive). Problem root unknown.

- In the Royal Guardian training course, guardian would often get stucked on borders and end up using the "stucked to border fix" which is not optimal

- When selected a guardian and pressed the beehive, it will not move towards it
- On rare occasions the bees (happee+) cannot enter beehive. (not first person experience)

+ CODE CLEANUP NOTES!!!
- Interation between bee and flower have lots of unnecessary variables
- Pick honey, go in flower, tell bee it's not inside flower   logic is ambigious - quite difficult to force the bee out of the fucking flower



